A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Campaigns, Series 5 FA440
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Campaigns, 1956-1970; 5; 98.04 Cubic Feet 216 containers including but not limited to: 45 letter document boxes, 167 legal document boxes.
  - 1968 U.S. Presidential Campaign, 8
    - Campaign Correpondence - ORA - PANZ, 1968 (Box 197, Folder 2374-2382)
    - Campaign Correpondence - PAO - PAX, 1968 (Box 198, Folder 2383-2392)
    - Campaign Correpondence - PAY - PERRIR, 1968 (Box 199, Folder 2393-2401)
    - Campaign Correpondence - PERRIS - PHZ, 1968 (Box 200, Folder 2402-2410)
    - Campaign Correpondence - PIA - POND, 1968 (Box 201, Folder 2411-2422)
    - Campaign Correpondence - PONE - PROR, 1968 (Box 202, Folder 2423-2431)
    - Campaign Correpondence - PROS - RAMZ, 1968 (Box 203, Folder 2432-2441)
    - Campaign Correpondence - RANA - RER, 1968 (Box 204, Folder 2442-2452)
    - Campaign Correpondence - REIS - RICHZ, 1968 (Box 205, Folder 2453-2463)
    - Campaign Correpondence - RICI - ROBERTS, 1968 (Box 206, Folder 2464-2473)
    - Campaign Correpondence - ROBERTSON - ROGGI, 1968 (Box 207, Folder 2474-2484)
    - Campaign Correpondence - ROGGJ - ROSZ, 1968 (Box 208, Folder 2485-2495)
    - Campaign Correpondence - ROTA - RUZ, 1968 (Box 209, Folder 2496-2506)
    - Campaign Correpondence - RV - SANDE, 1968 (Box 210, Folder 2507-2517)
    - Campaign Correpondence - SANDF - SCHAQ, 1968 (Box 211, Folder 2518-2528)
    - Campaign Correpondence - SCHAR - SCHNEI, 1968 (Box 212, Folder 2529-2537)
  - Campaign Photographs, 1956-1968; 9; 2.4 Cubic Feet
    This subseries consists of mostly black-and-white photographs from Nelson Rockefeller's successful New York gubernatorial campaigns and his three unsuccessful quests for the Republican Presidential nomination.
    - Photographs from the 1966 New York Gubernatorial Campaign (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 813-887)
      This box contains photographs removed from document files on the 1966 New York gubernatorial campaign. Refer to Subseries 4 on the 1966 campaign, Boxes 67 through 70, for the corresponding document files.
    - Photographs from the 1966 New York Gubernatorial Campaign (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 888-929)
      This box contains photographs removed from document files on the 1966 New York gubernatorial campaign. Refer to Subseries 4 on the 1966 campaign, Boxes 70 through 71, for the corresponding document files.
    - Photographs from the 1966 New York Gubernatorial Campaign and Slides from the 1968 U.S. Presidential Campaign, 1966, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 930-932)
      This box contains photographs removed from documents files on the 1966 gubernatorial campaign. Refer to Subseries 4 on the 1966 campaign, Box 71, for the corresponding document files. It also contains slides removed from document files on the 1968 presidential campaign. Refer to Subseries 8 on the 1968 campaign, Box 168, for the corresponding document files.
    - Photographs from Various Campaigns, 1956-1968 (Box 4)
      This box contains photographs removed from document files on several of the campaigns in this series: 1956, 1958, 1962, 1964, 1966, and 1968. Refer to the various subseries for the corresponding document files.